<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blogs>
	<blog><name>Samsung</name><date>2017-04-18</date><title><h2>The Hidden Innovations within the Samsung Galaxy S8 and S8+</h2></title><content>The Samsung Galaxy S8 and S8+, with its jaw dropping Infinity Display and silky smooth performance speed, bring mobile experience to the new level. As good as it looks amazing on the outside, the old adage “it’s what’s inside that counts” still holds true.
While the users enjoy a new standard of mobile experience with surprisingly futuristic design and functionalities of the new Samsung Galaxy S8 and S8+, numerous innovative components, such as the Exynos 9 Series (8895) processor built on 10nm FinFET process, the advanced image sensors or the OLED display driver IC for the Infinity Display, within the device are hard at work to handle various complicated tasks in the most efficient and optim</content></blog>
<blog><name>indianexpress</name><date>2017-11-02</date><title>Apple iPhone X review </title><content>Every Apple iPhone rides a hype machine. But the Apple iPhone X has been unprecedented even by Cupertino standards, managing to stay on top of popular imagination for well over a month when it was first unveiled for the world. While the jury is still out of whether it has impacted the sales of the iPhone 8 series despite the differential in pricing, it is clear that this phone has been able to capture consumer interest across the world. Over the next few days we will look at different aspects of the what is arguably the most premium mass production phone in the world at the moment. 
Apple iPhone X price in India: Rs 89,000+</content></blog>
<blog><name>Mashable</name><date>2017-11-03</date><title>The Social Media Guide</title><content>If you haven’t heard of “The Social Media Guide,” you just might be living under an old Commodore 64. Updated constantly, and nearly always entertaining, Mashable takes the worlds of Twitter, Facebook, entertainment, news, and everything else techies are talking about and, well, mashes it up into the kind of blog casserole we just can’t get enough of.</content></blog>
 s
<blog><name>Gizmodo</name><date>2017-11-09</date><title>“lost” next-gen Apple iPhone</title><content>Pretty much known as the TMZ of tech after they paid for a “lost” next-gen Apple iPhone — the fallout became front-page news across the world. Scandals aside, Gizmodo’s been a must-follow site for a long time, with tons of relevant posts, a youthful vibe, and some of the funnier commenters on the Internet.

</content></blog>
<blog><name>GigaOM</name><date>2017-11-08</date><title></title><content>If you’re looking for what’s next, look no further. Om Malik’s creation has grown into one of the largest blogs worldwide, and it’s all due to focusing on what’s new. News and analysis on Web 2.0, technologies and startups, social media, gaming — you name it, GigaOM has it covered. That’s what happens when you have a team of 12 technology-obsessed writers (six of which have authored over 100 posts each)</content></blog>
<blog><name>ZDNet</name><date>2017-11-07</date><title>ZiffNet</title><content>In online terms, 10 years is a lifetime and 20 is an eternity. How long ZDNet has been in existence makes this go-to tech website (formerly “ZiffNet”) an anomaly among blogs. Founded in 1991, formerly on CompuServe and Prodigy, ZDNet was purchased in 2000 by CNET (CBS Interactive), and reports on a variety of tech news. While they focus heavily on the usual suspects (Apple, Microsoft, Google), ZDNet also features product reviews, software downloads and tons of news and analysis on tech businesses and issues.</content></blog>
</blogs>
